Guide to the William Shockley Papers SC0222
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-198
  - National Academy of Sciences
    - National Research Council - National Academy of Science, 1976 Nov 2 (Box 124, Folder 56)
    - Election of Vice President and Four Councilors Ballot, 1989 Jan 16 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Van Vleck Hassle - National Academy of Sciences, 1968 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Letter to Members (reprint), 1971-1973 (Box 138, Folder 38)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Resolution, 1973 Apr 25 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Nikkei Electronics Magazines, 1976; 5 Japanese Magazines about technology and Shockley The Path to the Conception of the Junction Transistor, IEEE Trans. Vol. ED-23, No. 7, 597-620, July 1976 was translated into Japanese and published into four parts by Nikkei Electronics: Part 1: 5-30, No. 161, 110-120 Part 2: 6-13, No. 162, 145-159 Part 3: 6-27, No. 163, 141-154 Part 4: 7-11, No. 164, 153-173 Published again in Nikkei Books in the entirety in 1981: 4-20, 71, and 75-109 (Box 103)
  - Neurosciences Research Program, MIT, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    Notes from a course WS took on brain science.
  - Nobel Prize
    - Nobel Prize Literature (1 of 2), 1951-1986 (Box 134, Folder 21)
    - Nobel Prize Literature (2 of 2), 1951-1986 (Box 134, Folder 22)
    - Swedish Royal Academy of Sciences Nobel Committee for Physics - Proposal Invitation, 1971-1980 (Box 139, Folder 49)
  - Oakley Sutton Management Corp. (OSM), 1986 (Box 111, Folder 36)
  - On Urban Homicide: A Statistical Analysis - Working Paper, 1974 Sep 26 (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - "P" Series
    - P232.010 - Charles H. Townes, 1970 May 23 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - P232.010 - Congressional Record, 1970 May 18 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Political/ P-Series, 1974-1982 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - P-Series Index, 1981 Aug 9 - 1983 Dec 1 (Box 116, Folder 69)
    - P-515, 1982 Apr 12 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - P-512.1, 1982 Apr 5 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Papers Submitted to Phi Delta Kappan, 1976 Nov-Dec (Box 138, Folder 53)
  - Passports, Assocation Cards, etc., 1947-1993; Both Emmy's and William's passports are in this box Passports, Association Cards, International Certificates of Vaccination, War Department Identification (Box 118)
  - Pass-Fail and Tenure - Jenkin Jones, 1972 Mar 4-5 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - Patents (Box 60)
    Unfoldered correspondence, notes and other material related to some of WS' ninety patents, including work for Bell Telephone, Clevite, and other companies.
  - Pearson, "Shockley on Eugenics and Race", 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Roger Pearson correspondence with Emmy Shockley concerning a biography of WS for the Pioneer Fund. Also includes drafts and notes.
  - Pioneer Fund
    - Pioneer Fund press clippings and correspondence, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - The Review Article - Pioneer Fund, 1991 Mar 8 (Box 143, Folder 43)
    - Incoming Correspondence to Emmy Shockley from Pioneer Fund re U. of Delware, 1990 May 1 (Box 143, Folder 44)
    - Articles & Clippings Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 1), 1993-1997 (Box 143, Folder 71)
      Box 143 is a box containing clippings, articles, and correspondence mostly published/sent after Shockley's death. Pioneer Fund is a non-profit foundation to "advance the scientific study of heredity & human differences".
    - Articles & Clippings Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 2), 1993-1997 (Box 143, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 3), 1997-1998 (Box 143, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 4), 1997-1998 (Box 143, Folder 74)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 5), 1997-2000 (Box 143, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 6), 1997-1999 (Box 143, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 7), 1999-2000 (Box 143, Folder 77)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 8), 1999-2000 (Box 143, Folder 78)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund (Part 9), 1995 (Box 143, Folder 79)
    - Correspondence Sent from the Pioneer Fund - Burrelle's World Wide Web Edition Notices (Box 170)
  - Playboy interview, 1979-1980 (Box 35)
    Voluminous drafts and correspondence for an August 1980 article by Syl Jones, who had profiled WS previously for Modern Medicine.
    - "Actual Versus Published Interviews of Shockley for Playboy", 1980 Jul 10 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Playboy Interview: William Shockley (Box 111, Folder 29)
    - Playboy - 6 Versions/KOFF, 1969 Feb-Mar (Box 121, Folder 75)
  - Photographs
    - photographs, 1948-1986 (Box 91, 93, 95)
    - Nobel Prize scrapbook, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Japan trip scrapbook, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - WS at four months, 1909 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - various WS portraits (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Photos loaned for reproduction - Nobel Prize, yachting (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - photos of Emmy and May Shockley [removed from frames] (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - unidentified men at dinner c.1960s (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - large WS portraits (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Shockley Thesis Photos (Box 112, 112)
      General note
      Some of the photos are badly damaged but can still be looked at if held up to the light, have been packaged seperately to keep further damage from occurring.
    - Climbing Photographs, 1946-1951 (Box 117)
    - W=S and Pope John Paul II, Vatican Visit, 1983 May (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - Transistor Photograph Binder, circa 1940s-1950s; Photographs of Shockley and his team designing, building, and testing the transistor. Photographs of Shockley presenting the transitor to an audience Photographs of Shockley receving the Nobel Prize in Switzerland. (Box 137)
    - Photograph Binder of William Shockley, Photographs of Shockley publicly speaking & walking around with other scientists Photograph of the transistor on a 8 cents stamp (Box 137)
    - Autographed Ready for Reproduction or Request for a Photo, circa 1970s (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Political
    - political campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 63)
      WS ran as a Republican candidate for the U.S. Senate in 1982, and received 7000 votes in the primary. Included are campaign materials (brochures, speech transcripts, etc.), state and federal forms and guides, and campaign material from other candidates.
    - Shockley for the Senate of California Campaign, 1982-1983 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Federal Election Comission - Pub. Records Info Sheet, 1977-1978; An "E" Index for Jelms & Thurmond (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Zeller & Letica, Inc. - Contributes to Conseructive Political Causes 3034 - Addresses (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Political Campaign - Letter, 1982 Apr 12 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Summary of Contributions - Republican Party, 1988 Nov 1 (Box 116, Folder 71)
    - IBM Magnetic Card, Political Statement US Senator, 1982 Feb 10 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Summary of Contributions to the Republican Party, 1986-1988 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Report No. 93-381 from the Senate, 1973 Aug 7 (Box 138, Folder 28)
    - Political News Articles, 1976 Sep-Nov (Box 138, Folder 57)
  - Polygraphs
    - Polygraphs Appeal, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Presentations
    - Graph on IQ & Class (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Graphs for Presentation on Black Families (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Figs. Trans. El. Dev. (Figures of Transistors' Early Developement?), 1976 Jul (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Graphs for Presentation on IQ & Race, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Statistics Sign on Children/ Women, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Anti/Dsygenics Sign (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Christian Eugenics Society Presentation, 1973 Aug 24 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Byram Hills High School Presentation, 1974 May 23 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Reading Copies for Bridgeport, Toronto, & Monterey, 1969 Dec (Box 130, Folder 21)
      Copies for presentations in various cities.
    - Commonwealth Lecture Drafts, 1967 Jan 13 (Box 142)
  - Purdue University
    - Dept. of Psychological Sciences, 1973-1988 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Putnam, Carleton
    - Correspondence - Carleton Putnam, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence - Carleton Putnam, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Project 2XX0601, 1971-1972; Research on Methodology to Reduce the Environment-Heredity Uncertainty Including Ethnic and Racial Aspect Donors for the project/research Proposal for the extension of the project (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - "R" & "T" Series
    This formal series for scientific papers was assigned numerical codes in a sequence with a "T" (and sometimes "R") prefix. Nearly all have WS as one author (most have more than one author). T-1, from 1936, is an offprint with R.P. Johnson at MIT. Many are Bell Telephone Lab Technical Memoranda, some as late as 1968. There is a seven year gap between T-17 and T-18 during World War II. The series also includes drafts, lecture transcripts, teaching aids, correspondence, notes, and clippings. R106-R153 span the years of 1962-1984 with a gap between 1972-1984. R137 contains original Lorentz Transformation Seminar manuscript.
    - 1-33 (Box 13)
    - 34-62 (Box 14)
    - 63-79 (Box 15)
    - 80-113 (Box 16)
    - 115-139 (Box 17)
    - 145-153 (Box 18)
    - 106-153, 1963-1984 (Box 179)
    - 153, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - 79-92, 1957-1958 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - 92-148, 1959-1968 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - 79, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - 153, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - 153 - Misc, 1977 Jan (Box 123, Folder 41)
    - 153 - Includes letter to Geoffrey W. Taylor, 1976 Jul (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - R153-R78.5, 1956-1976 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Realia
    - Microscopes, calculators, a slide rule, other unidentified electronic and mechanical objects. (Box 68)
    - Ice Climbing Axe (Box 177)
  - Reference - WS, 1987 Oct (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - reprints, Abstracts (A) series
    This formal series of abstracts for scientific papers was assigned numerical codes in a sequence with a "A" prefix.
    - 20-45, 1951-1971 (Box 179)
    - 20-45, 1951-1971 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - reprints, Information (I) series
    Newspaper and magazine articles, editorials, correspondence, essays, transcripts, and other material, nearly all concerning WS and his second career promoting what he termed “human quality” issues. This series was maintained by WS for reference and distribution purposes. Each file was assigned a number with the prefix “I” (presumably for Informational). These files are approximately chronological and grouped around significant events (such as classroom disruptions, panels, debates and media appearances, SWOPSI hearings, and NAS meetings). Most material is photocopied; however some original clippings, press releases, drafts and signed correspondence is present. Blue copies were for FREED distribution. Items related to his run for senate have a “P” prefix. There is a full index in Box 71.
    - 1-57, 1963-1967 (Box 21)
    - 58-126, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
    - 127-180, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
    - 181-214, 1969-1970 (Box 24)
    - 216-248, 1970-1971 (Box 25)
    - 249-288, 1971 (Box 26)
    - 289-327, 1971-1972 (Box 27)
    - 328-385, 1972-1973 (Box 28)
    - 387-432, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
    - 468-520, 1976-1983 (Box 31)
    - Index (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 433-466, 1974-1976 (Box 30)
    - reprints, Information (I) series [Bound] (Box 86)
      Bound Information (I) series. Reprints of newspaper and magazine articles, editorials, correspondence, essays, transcripts, and other material, nearly all concerning WS and his second career promoting what he termed “human quality” issues. These files are approximately chronological and grouped around significant events (such as classroom disruptions, panels, debates and media appearances, SWOPSI hearings, and NAS meetings). See also reprints, Information (I) series.
      - 1-54.8, 1963-1967 (Box 86)
      - 55-99, 1967-1968 (Box 86)
      - 100-159, 1968-1969 (Box 86)
      - 160-199, 1969 (Box 86)
      - 200-218.4, 1969-1970 (Box 86)
      - 219-248.1, 1970-1971 (Box 86)
      - 248.2-288.0.2, 1971 (Box 86)
    - 470 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - reprints, Numbered series
    Newspaper and magazine articles, editorials, correspondence, essays, transcripts, and other material, nearly all concerning WS and his second career promoting what he termed “human quality” issues. This series was maintained by WS for reference and distribution purposes. Each file was assigned a number and is most likely related to the Information (I) series with duplication of the (I) series likely. These files are approximately chronological and grouped around significant events (such as classroom disruptions, panels, debates and media appearances, SWOPSI hearings, and NAS meetings). Most material is photocopied; however some original clippings, press releases, drafts and signed correspondence is present. Some files include IBM magnetic cards. Blue copies were for FREED distribution.
    Within the numbered series there are 3 parallel filings of 445-480, which include some duplication, but also some unique material across the parallel files.
    - 1-183, 1963-1969 (Box 83)
    - 184-520, 1969-1983 (Box 80)
    - 211-265, 1970-1971 (Box 87)
    - 266-349.1 (Box 88)
      There is a gap between 291 and 343
    - 350.1-444, 1972-1975 (Box 82)
    - 446-478, 1975-1976 (Box 84)
    - 445-480, 1975-1976 (Box 81)
    - 456-495, 1975-1978 (Box 85)
  - reprints, WS
    WS scientific papers, reprints, and miscellaneous small research projects. Related to the “T” series, with some duplication likely. Material is unfoldered and arranged chronologically. Also contains notes, correspondence, other reprints and papers, lectures, and unpublished drafts. Includes work from Bell Labs, a WWII military report, and a set of bound reprint files.
    - 1944-1962 (Box 58)
    - 1962-1975 (Box 59)
    - 1978-1986 (Box 60)
  - reprints, others
    Scientific papers, reprints, and related correspondence by other researchers, unfoldered and arranged by principal author. The majority cover physics and transistor technology, but there are also genetics and demographic studies, including several by Arthur Jensen. Many are inscribed to or annotated by WS.
    - A-J (Box 64)
      - 1956 Nobel Prize and something from 1968, 1956-1968; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 64)
    - J-R (Box 65)
    - R-S (Box 66)
    - S-W and misc. by subject (Box 67)
  - reprints, Hustler Magazine
    - Articles & Clippings, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - reprints, Correspondence
    - Carleton Putnam to Dr. Frederick Seitz re Shockley 'Environment Heredity Uncertainty', 1967 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, reprints - John H. Northrop, 1967-1969 (Box 114, Folder 43)
  - Reprints, Mike Culbert, 1970 May 26 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Research in Psychiatry, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Science Education, 1965-1970 (Box 71)
    Files related to WS' efforts to develop better methods of teaching science, Including the Shockley-Stanford Science Education Project's "The Conservation of Energy Concept in Ninth Grade General Science," and Carnegie Grant material.
    - Carnegie Grant
      - Misc. Correspondence re. Carnegie Grant, 1966 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Misc., 1965-1966 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - "Creative Analysis" Research (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - A Proposal by W. Shockley, For a grant from teh Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Education (granted in July 1965) (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Educational Records Bureau
      - Educational Records Bureau - Manuscript for Human Quality Problems & Research Taboos (including photos), 1968-1969 (Box 121, Folder 52)
      - Educational Records Bureau - Special Refs, MS, Booklets, Clippings, etc., 1967-1968 (Box 121, Folder 53)
      - Incoming Correspondence - Educational Records Bureau Presentation, 1968 Feb-Nov (Box 121, Folder 54)
      - Incoming Correspondence - Educational Records Bureau, 1968 Dec 3 (Box 121, Folder 56)
      - ERB Master - Human Quality Problems and Research Taboos, 1969 Jan 2 (Box 121, Folder 62)
      - "Ed. Rec. Bu in Progress" Folder, 1968-1969 (Box 121, Folder 63)
    - Science Teaching
      - Science Education - Structure of Intellect, 1960-1963 (Box 123, Folder 18)
      - Science Teaching - University of Illinois Elementary School Science Project, 1961-1963 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - Science Teaching - University of Illinois Elementary School Science Project, 1961-1963 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Science Teaching - Reprint File Index (R-Number), 1994 Aug (Box 129, Folder 19)
      - Science Teaching - Reprint File Index, 1987 Feb 1 (Box 129, Folder 20)
      - Science Teaching - Working Index, 1985 Aug 16 (Box 129, Folder 24)
      - Science Teaching - Final Report on "The Conservation of Energy Concept in Ninth Grade General Science" (BTL Copy), 1968 Feb (Box 139, Folder 52)
      - Science Teaching - Notes on Alexander W. Astin "Undergraduate Achievement and Institutional Excellence", 1968 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Science Teaching - Walter Gong, 1972 Jul-Aug (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Science Teaching - Misc., 1965 (Box 142, Folder 5)
        Includes correspondencefrom Albert Lipton & Eugene Brunelle, notes on telephone conversation with Richard Crutchfield.
      - Science Teaching Lecture Travel Kit, 1966-1967 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Articulated Science Teaching, Misc., 1966 Apr-Jun (Box 142, Folder 26)
    - Sales Pitch to American Management Association for "Thinking About Thinking Improves Thinking", 1969 Aug 1 (Box 142, Folder 27)
    - inventory record, Shockley-Stanford Science Education Project (Box 90)
    - Student Self-Report Project with Results & Graphs, 1970 Apr-May (Folder 4)
    - 4th International Symposium on Educational Testing - Antwerp Blegium, 1980 Jun 24-27 (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - Creative Analysis - High School List, 1965-1966 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Research - Rational Thinking: Progressive Matrices Test Results (students) (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Research - Rational Reasoning: Bell Laboratories Standard Progressive Matrices Test, 1966 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Publications - "Reviewof Educational Research", 1971 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Health Educational Tests, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - "The Conservation of Energy Concept in Ninth Grade General Science" - Final Report, 1968 Feb (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - High School Engery Logic Unit (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Teching Scientific Thinking at the High School Level, 1964 Oct (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - The Conservation of Energy Concept in Ninth Grade General Science - Final Report, 1968 Feb (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University News Service, Science Teaching, 1967 Jan 27 (Box 142, Folder 25)
    - "Mental Tools for Scientific Thinking with Applications to Semiconductors," New York University, 1966 Dec 15 (Box 142, Folder 28)
  - Schonemann, Peter H.
    - Correspondence & Printed material, 1985-1988 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Reprints - EB Wilson & PH Schonemann, 1981-1986 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Peter H. Schonemann, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Peter H. Schonemann - Intelligence, 1985-1986 (Box 139, Folder 51)
  - Shockley Family and Personal
    This series contains diaries, notebooks, artwork and correspondence, primarily from WS' parents William Hillman and May Bradford Shockley. The majority of Shockley family material in this accession was saved by WS following May's death in 1977. WS wrote about the experience in a commemorative booklet included here. May’s own files are mostly small sketches and paintings. Most photographs not attached to notebook pages have been moved to the Photographs series. See also May Shockley papers in first accession Series IV, other WHS diaries in Box 12 of the first accession, and the William Hillman Shockley papers, circa 1860-circa 1920 (SC1108)..
    William and May Shockley approached the rearing of their only child in a very scientific manner, and subsequently there is a considerable amount of detail about the birth and childhood of WS (known here as “Billy”), including charts of his diet, health and growth and lists of books read to, as well as artwork, a lock of hair, and even a splinter removed from his face after a mishap on a front porch. References to his inquisitiveness, temper, stubbornness, and manual dexterity suggest much of what later characterized him.
    The group of notebooks by WHS provide many insights about the Shockleys and life in Palo Alto in the teens. These notebooks feature diaries (some also doubling as correspondence to family members), notes, lists, clippings (most from the Daily Palo Alto News), and material related to his role in the Simplified Spelling movement. Some correspondence has been pasted in notebooks, including a telegram from William Randolph Hearst telegram in 1916.
    The diaries make note of WHS’ involvement with the Engineers Club (of which he was Vice President), as well as his mining, real estate and other business ventures. Also revealed are interactions with friends (including the Hoovers), neighbors, and professors at Stanford, as well as accounts of excursions to Lake Lagunita, La Honda and elsewhere. WHS wrote about World War I even before the U.S. entered the conflict, and when Camp Fremont was built in Menlo Park, WHS took an interest in the recreation of soldiers. May was also active in food rationing, home economics and Belgian relief efforts during the war. Finally, the diaries chronicle the family’s travels in Los Angeles, New York, Florida, and Louisiana (where they bought a pet alligator), as well as London (where they were living when WS was born) and continental Europe.
    Also grouped here are some unrelated WS personal files, such as material concerning his mountain climbing and magic trick interests, an art class notebook from Hollywood High School, an autograph book from Caltech, and a 1931 exercise pamphlet in which he posed as a model. This series also features later genealogy-related correspondence between WS and others.
    Shockley, May Bradford; Shockley, William Hillman
    - WHS notebooks and diaries, 1909-1925
      - WS diaries and day planners, 1938-1989
        Day planners, notebooks, and annotated desk calendars, unfoldered and arranged chronologically. Some were used only sporadically, particularly 1989. These notebooks contain both personal and professional information; 1955 notebooks have family correspondence, notes and correspondence about his divorce from Jean Shockley, as well as notes from his initial meeting with Beckman. 1961-1980 notebooks were numbered 10-35 and begin with his extended recovery from a serious automobile accident. Bohemian Club notebooks were transferred to other BC material in Box 62, and a 1932 autograph book from Caltech (including an autograph from Linus Pauling) was moved to the Shockley family/personal series.
        - 1938-1959 (Box 44)
        - 1960-1972 (Box 43)
        - 1973-1989 (Box 45)
        - Diaries and Calendars, 1948-1989; Notebooks,1953-1989; Bell Telephone Laboratories Telephone Directory,1954-1955; Telephone Book; Stock Ledgers,1961-1966; Typing Exercises,1986; Baedeker's Guide Books- "Rhine"; "Egypt"; "Osterreich-Ungarn"; "Canada" (Box 76)
      - misc. notes, mostly concerning household business, health and diet. includes WS baby notes, c.1909-1920 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - "Four" notes, clippings, photographs, lists, correspondence, etc., circa 1917-1920 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - diary (with photographs and negatives), 1909-03-19 - 1910-10-04 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - diary, 1910-10-04 - 1911-08-23 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - diary, 1911-1913 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - "1A" packing lists, WS report cards and baby journal, c.1915-1923 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - diary, 1913-04-12 - 1915-07 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - ["Two"?] diary, 1916-1917 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - diary, correspondence, 1916-10 - 1922-12-04 (Box 33, Folder 9)